With "The Shining" and "Misery" Stephen King scared you to
death. Now, he's going to scare you back to life.
Sometimes They Come Back is a horror, tv movie film directed by Tom McLoughlin.
Desperate for a job to help him support his family, Jim Norman takes a position teaching high school in the
town where his brother was murdered in front of him by teenage bullies twenty-seven years before.
The teens who committed the crime are long dead, but now the kids in Jim's new class keep
dying and being replaced by new students who look like the deceased hoodlums.
Jim Norman, played by Tim Matheson.
Sally Norman, played by Brooke Adams.
Lawson, played by Robert Rusler.
Wayne Norman, played by Chris Demetral.
Scott Norman, played by Robert Hy Gorman.
Mueller, played by William Sanderson.
Sometimes They Come Back is a 1991 American made-for-television horror film
based on the 1974 short story of the same name by Stephen King.
Originally optioned as a segment of the 1985 feature film Stephen King's Cat's Eye, it
was developed into a separate feature by producer Dino De Laurentiis.
The film explores themes of high school, loss of
loved one, bully, train, childhood.
The tone is dark.